utteraccess.com 2009-11-24

# UtterAccess Discussion Forums - Privacy Policy

| 

**Welcome to UtterAccess.com!**

The UtterAccess.com (UA) privacy policy exists to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices of UtterAccess.

__Information Automatically Logged__  
We use your IP address to help administer UA. Specifically, IP addresses are automatically recorded to help us track any potential malicious use of UtterAccess.

__Cookies__  
UtterAccess uses cookies to save an encrypted version of your password. If you choose 'remember me!', you will not have to enter your password each time you visit.  
Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on UtterAccess.  
Google's use of the [DoubleClick DART cookie](http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/faq.aspx) enables it to serve ads to UtterAccess users based on their visit to UA and other sites on the Internet.  
UtterAccess users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy.](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html)  
__Registration Forms__  
When you sign up and become a member of the UA family, the registration form requires minimal contact information (a valid email address), and a unique identifier ( _username_ ).

 **UtterAccess.com does not and will not sell or transmit any personal information you have provided under any circumstances. This is our promise.**

Your registered email address may be used by UtterAccess Administrators and Editors to contact you if and when necessary, and to provide a destination should you choose to subscribe to any of the forum features we offer. Unique identifiers ( _usernames_ ) are required for all UtterAccess members to associate them with the posts they author.

__External Links__  
UtterAccess contains links to many other websites. UtterAccess is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of any other website.  
__Public Forums__  
UtterAccess makes many of the forums available to the world. Please remember that information disclosed in these areas becomes public information. Please exercise caution before disclosing any personal information.  
__Security__  
UtterAccess has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. The data provided when registering for membership of the discussion forum is stored in secure databases, in secure servers within a secure data-center.   
__Data Quality/Access__  
UtterAccess gives registered members the option to change or modify any aspect of their personal profile. Should a registered member desire a change to their Username, they must contact an Administrator.  
__Contacting UtterAccess__  
If you have any questions regarding this privacy statement, the practices of UtterAccess, or your dealings with UtterAccess, please feel free to contact us at anytime.

The UtterAccess.com privacy policy has been updated as of 2009-03-13 to explicitly reflect the use of Google's interest-based advertising.
